A Guide to the Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. records FA025
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2, 1875, 1878, 1916-2001 1969-2001; 2; 28 Cubic Feet
  - Grants, 1964, 1969-2001; 3
    - Discretionary Grants, 1974, 1977-1998; 3
      - Foreign Policy Association, 1981, 1984-1988 (Reel 24, Frame 7)
      - Friends of the Bruce Museum, 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 216)
      - Friends of the Ferguson Library, 1990 (Reel 24, Frame 218)
      - Friends of the Philharmonic, 1979, 1983-1986, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 220)
      - Friends of Post 53, 1988-1992 (Reel 24, Frame 229)
      - Glen Echo Fire Department, 1990 (Reel 24, Frame 232)
      - God's Love We Deliver, 1988-1989 (Reel 24, Frame 234)
      - Good Shepherd House of Hospitality, 1988-1990 (Reel 24, Frame 236)
      - Goodspeed Opera House, 1987-1991 (Reel 24, Frame 238)
      - Goodwill Fire Company, Number 2, 1978 (Reel 24, Frame 277)
      - Grace Evangelical Lutheran Church, 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 281)
      - Greek Cultural Center Endowment Fund, 1981, 1984, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 283)
      - Greenwich Advisory Council of Youth and Drugs, Inc., 1982-1985 (Reel 24, Frame 285)
      - Grant Foundation, 1985-1986 (Reel 24, Frame 291)
      - Historical Society of the Town of Greenwich, 1988-1990, 1997 (Reel 24, Frame 293)
      - Holy Infant Church, 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 332)
      - Hospice of Stamford, 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 334)
      - Hunger Relief and Development, Inc., 1987 (Reel 24, Frame 336)
      - Hurricane Island Outward Bound School, 1991 (Reel 24, Frame 338)
      - International Rescue Committee, Inc., 1989-1990 (Reel 24, Frame 340)
      - James Howard Scholarship Fund, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 342)
      - Jesuit Seminary and Mission Bureau, 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 345)
      - The Kennedy Center, Inc., 1983-1984, 1986-1993 (Reel 24, Frame 362)
      - Kolbe Cathedral High School, 1983-1985, 1988-1992 (Reel 24, Frame 400)
      - Land Trust of Darien, Inc., 1988-1991 (Reel 24, Frame 408)
      - Little Sisters of the Poor (Queen of Peace Residence), 1984 (Reel 24, Frame 410)
      - Malachi House, 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 416)
      - Manhattan School of Music, 1988, 1998 (Reel 24, Frame 418)
      - Marlboro School of Music, 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 424)
      - Marquette University, 1978, 1986, 1988-1989 (Reel 24, Frame 472)
      - Marymount Manhattan College, 1988-1989 (Reel 24, Frame 474)
      - The Merry-Go-Round (Mews), Inc., 1988-1989 (Reel 24, Frame 481)
      - Miriam Osborn Memorial Home Association, 1987-1988 (Reel 24, Frame 483)
      - Monadnock Health Foundation, 1990 (Reel 24, Frame 485)
      - Monadnock Workshop, 1986 (Reel 24, Frame 487)
      - Muskingum College, 1981-1982, 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 489)
      - Nature Conservancy - Connecticut, 1984, 1990 (Reel 24, Frame 498)
      - Nazareth Life Center, 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 502)
      - New England Surgical Society and Charitable Foundation, 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 507)
      - New Hampshire Task Force of Child Abuse and Neglect, 1986 (Reel 24, Frame 509)
      - Northgate Church of God, 1985, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 511)
      - Norwalk Seaport Association, 1987 (Reel 24, Frame 513)
      - Norwalk Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1971, 1977-1981, 1984-1985 (Reel 24, Frame 516)
      - Oddfellows Playhouse, 1981, 1986-1989 (Reel 24, Frame 558)
      - Our Lady Star of the Sea Church/School Association, 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 616)
      - Park Avenue Christian Church, 1984-1986 (Reel 24, Frame 618)
      - Peace Corps, 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 620)
      - Pennsylvania Hospital, 1990 (Reel 24, Frame 622)
      - Presbyterian Church of Thomas, 1978, 1984-1986, 1991 (Reel 24, Frame 624)
      - Ronald McDonald House, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 634)
      - St. Alban's Episcopal Church, 1978, 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 636)
      - St. Andrew Avellino School, 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 638)
      - St. Andrew's Sewanee School, 1990 (Reel 24, Frame 640)
      - Saint Francis Home, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 642)
      - St. Jerome Church, 1977-1986 (Reel 24, Frame 644)
      - Saint John's Episcopal Church, 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 646)
      - St. John's Park War Memorial Fund, 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 648)
      - St. Joseph's Church, 1983-1986 (Reel 24, Frame 650)
      - St. Luke's Episcopal Church, 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 652)
      - St. Mary's Church - Reverend Patrick Mooney, 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 654)
      - Saint Paul's Church, 1987-1989 (Reel 24, Frame 656)
      - St. Peter's Preparatory, 1977-1979, 1985-1990 (Reel 24, Frame 658)
      - St. Thomas More Church, Boynton Beach, Florida, 1980-1981 (Reel 24, Frame 693)
      - Sacred Heart Church School, undated (Reel 24, Frame 695)
      - Society for the Protection of New Hampshire Forests, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 697)
      - Stamford Boy's Club, 1985-1986 (Reel 24, Frame 699)
      - Thomas Presbyterian Church, 1978, 1984, 1986 (Reel 24, Frame 701)
      - Tri-County Scholarship Fund, 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 703)
      - Trinity Church on the Green, 1978, 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 706)
      - Trinity Evangelical Lutheran Church, 1990 (Reel 24, Frame 708)
      - Trinity-Pawling School, 1984, 1986 (Reel 24, Frame 710)
      - United Church of Westville, 1985, 1987 (Reel 24, Frame 712)
      - United States Association of Former Members of Congress, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 714)
      - The University of Cape Town Fund, Inc., 1990 (Reel 24, Frame 722)
      - Vincentian Fathers, 1986-1990 (Reel 24, Frame 724)
      - The Visiting Nurse Association of New Canaan, 1979, 1987 (Reel 24, Frame 735)
      - Whitby School, 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 737)
      - The Wild Geese, 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 739)
    - Education Grants, 1974-1999; 4
      In support of education, several targeted programs were established to recognize the needs of private secondary school students without financial resources and to provide them the opportunity to attend these institutions. The support to private schools aimed to expand the student base beyond the traditionally financially elite. Educators at these institutions benefited from sabbaticals to pursue curriculum development and other incentives that helped schools retain qualified but overworked and underpaid instructors. Materials relating to these grants are found in Series 3.4.5.
      The Charles E. Culpeper Fellowships in the social sciences were an important part of the assistance extended to individuals to provide full support for a post-doctoral student in the social sciences with particular emphasis on public policy studies. The Foundation also supported undergraduate education in the liberal arts and sciences at undergraduate private institutions and library technology in its pioneering stages.
      Series 3.4 is arranged in five sub-subseries:
      Sub-subseries 1 - Education, General Support Grants
      Sub-subseries 2 - Foreign Language Education Program Grants
      Sub-subseries 3 - Library Automation Program Grants
      Sub-subseries 4 - Library Preservation Grants
      Sub-subseries 5 - Secondary School Grants
      - Education, General Support Grants, 1974-1997; 1
        This subseries details grant awards which are not included in other categories.
        Series 3.4.1 is arranged alphabetically by institution name.
        - Series 3.4.1 - Grants - Education Grants - Education, General Support Grants, 1974-1997 (Reel 24, Frame 742)
        - Association of American Colleges, 1986, 1990-1992 (Reel 24, Frame 743)
        - Babson College, 1989-1990 (Reel 24, Frame 808)
        - Blair Academy, 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 845)
        - Center for Excellence in Education, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 859)
        - Children's Institute, 1989-1990 (Reel 24, Frame 1051)
        - Choate Rosemary Hall, 1989-1990, 1993-1997 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
        - City College of the City University of New York, 1988-1989 (Reel 25, Frame 195)
        - College of the Atlantic, 1993-1996 (Reel 25, Frame 210)
        - Columbia University School of Law, 1985-1986, 1990-1994 (Reel 25, Frame 262)
        - Connecticut Association of Independent Schools, 1985-1986, 1990-1994 (Reel 25, Frame 265)
        - The Cooke Foundation for Special Education, 1989-1990 (Reel 25, Frame 279)
        - Council for Aid to Education, Inc., 1987 (Reel 25, Frame 300)
        - The Council of Independent Colleges, 1987-1992, 1994 (Reel 25, Frame 302)
        - Elizabeth O'Hara Walsh School, 1977-1988 (Reel 25, Frame 439)
        - Fairfield University, 1974-1982 (Reel 25, Frame 620)
        - George Washington University, 1995-1997 (Reel 25, Frame 769)
        - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary, 1989-1994 (Reel 25, Frame 792)
        - Hampshire College, 1988-1990 (Reel 25, Frame 963)
        - Heathwood Hall Episcopal School, 1985 (Reel 25, Frame 1019)
        - Illinois Benedictine College, 1989-1991 (Reel 25, Frame 1037)
        - Indiana University, 1981-1985, 1987 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
        - The Johns Hopkins Fund, 1975-1979 (Reel 26, Frame 18)
        - Linden Hill School, 1992 (Reel 26, Frame 112)
        - Martin De Porres School, 1981-1982, 1985-1987, 1989 (Reel 26, Frame 114)
        - Morehouse College, 1987-1988 (Reel 26, Frame 158)
        - Notre Dame School, 1985, 1987, 1990 (Reel 26, Frame 193)
        - Oberlin College, 1982-1993 (Reel 26, Frame 198)
        - Oberlin College, 1994-1997 (Reel 26, Frame 307)
        - Regis High School, 1978-1979, 1981, 1984-1992 (Reel 26, Frame 407)
        - St. George's School, 1981, 1991 (Reel 26, Frame 463)
        - St. Peter's College, 1968-1984, 1993 (Reel 26, Frame 466)
        - St. Peter's Prep, 1985, 1986, 1989-1990 (Reel 26, Frame 543)
        - Seattle University, 1985-1987 (Reel 26, Frame 555)
        - South Kent School, 1978, 1986-1987, 1991 (Reel 26, Frame 591)
        - Sponsors for Educational Opportunity, 1988 (Reel 26, Frame 593)
        - Studio in a School Association, Inc., 1995-1996 (Reel 26, Frame 627)
        - University of Mississippi, 1987-1998 (Reel 26, Frame 670)
        - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation, 1976-1983 (Reel 26, Frame 731)
        - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation, 1984-1988 (Reel 26, Frame 841)
      - Foreign Language Education Program Grants, 1982-1999; 2
        The Foundation established the Foreign Language Education Program to enhance language studies and to encourage international studies with a particular focus upon non-Western cultures. Language laboratories were established at colleges for this purpose, along with specific programs in support of language learning, cross-cultural studies programs, and East-West cultural and academic exchange.
        Series 3.4.2 is arranged alphabetically by institution name.
        - Series 3.4.2 - Grants - Education Grants - Foreign Language Education Program Grants, 1982-1999 (Reel 26, Frame 918)
        - Beloit College, 1984-1990 (Reel 26, Frame 919)
        - Bryn Mawr College, 1983-1985 (Reel 26, Frame 969)
        - Carnegie-Mellon University, 1991-1993 (Reel 26, Frame 1006)
        - Colby College, 1985, 1987-1988 (Reel 26, Frame 1058)
        - College of the Holy Cross, 1990-1994 (Reel 26, Frame 1105)
        - College of Mount St. Vincent, 1982-1983, 1987-1989, 1993-1995 (Reel 27, Frame 1)
        - The Consortium for Language Teaching and Learning, 1986-1990 (Reel 27, Frame 87)
        - The Consortium for Language Teaching and Learning, 1991-1996 (Reel 27, Frame 230)
        - Critical Languages and Area Studies Consortium, 1989-1992 (Reel 27, Frame 359)
        - Critical Languages and Area Studies Consortium, 1993-1995 (Reel 27, Frame 545)
        - Dillard University, 1990-1993, 1996 (Reel 27, Frame 665)
        - Foreign Language Education Program Questionnaire (A-G), 1996 (Reel 27, Frame 747)
        - Foreign Language Education Program Questionnaire (H-P), 1996 (Reel 27, Frame 1015)
        - Foreign Language Education Program Questionnaire (S-W), 1996 (Reel 27, Frame 1275)
          St. Mary's College is the only institution in this folder. The folder is continued on Reel 28, Frame 0001.
        - Foreign Language Education Program Questionnaire (S-W), 1996 (Reel 28, Frame 1)
        - Franklin and Marshall College, 1990-1997 (Reel 28, Frame 349)
        - Fresh Air Fund, 1972-1973, 1991-1996 (Reel 28, Frame 378)
        - Georgetown University, 1977-1979, 1982, 1986-1987, 1989-1991 (Reel 28, Frame 568)
        - Hampden-Sydney College, 1988-1990 (Reel 28, Frame 570)
        - Lake Forest College, 1983-1990 (Reel 28, Frame 601)
        - Lake Forest College, 1991-1992 (Reel 28, Frame 699)
        - Luther College, 1988-1989 (Reel 28, Frame 828)
        - Macalester College, 1991-1996 (Reel 28, Frame 868)
        - Millsaps College, 1990-1992 (Reel 28, Frame 1027)
        - Millsaps College, 1993-1996, 1999 (Reel 28, Frame 1187)
        - Mount Holyoke College, 1986-1991 (Reel 29, Frame 1)
        - Mount Holyoke College, 1992-1998 (Reel 29, Frame 89)
        - National Council on Foreign Language and International Studies, 1983, 1986, 1995 (Reel 29, Frame 319)
        - Norwich University, 1990-1992 (Reel 29, Frame 343)
        - Occidental College, 1989-1990 (Reel 29, Frame 388)
        - St. Olaf College, 1990-1992 (Reel 29, Frame 427)
        - Skidmore College, 1986-1988 (Reel 29, Frame 523)
        - 'Technology and Foreign Language Learning: A Report to the Charles E. Culpeper Foundation' - National Foreign Language Center, 1998 (Reel 29, Frame 564)
        - Toynbee Prize Foundation, 1989-1993-1995 (Reel 29, Frame 657)
        - University of Scranton, 1988-1991 (Reel 29, Frame 797)
        - Vassar College, 1983-1996 (Reel 29, Frame 916)
      - Library Automation Program Grants, 1982-1994; 3
        Over a ten year period, the Foundation pledged $3 million to library automation projects through twenty-eight grants, including grants to library consortia. In total, these grants benefited over fifty separate institutions. The program aimed to provide patrons with access to information resources and new services, and to manage financial resources more efficiently.
        Series 3.4.3 is arranged alphabetically by institution name.
        - Series 3.4.3 - Grants - Education Grants - Library Automation Program Grants, 1982-1994 (Reel 29, Frame 956)
        - Alfred University, 1989-1993 (Reel 29, Frame 957)
        - The Brookings Institution, 1984-1986, 1988-1992, 1994 (Reel 29, Frame 1033)
        - Children's Television Workshop Library Consortium, 1986-1993 (Reel 30, Frame 1)
        - Hampton University, 1982, 1992 (Reel 30, Frame 148)
        - Hood College, 1992 (Reel 30, Frame 164)
        - Hope College, 1987-1993 (Reel 30, Frame 191)
        - Library Automation Questionnaires (A-C), 1992 (Reel 30, Frame 303)
        - Library Automation Questionnaires (F-R), 1992 (Reel 30, Frame 510)
        - Library Automation Questionnaires (S-W), 1992 (Reel 30, Frame 718)
        - Loyola/Notre Dame Library, Inc., Baltimore, Maryland, 1990-1992 (Reel 30, Frame 936)
        - Messiah College, 1989-1992 (Reel 30, Frame 991)
        - Mountain College Library Network, 1992-1995 (Reel 30, Frame 1158)
        - Nebraska Wesleyan University, 1991-1994 (Reel 31, Frame 1)
        - Pace University, 1990-1992, 1997 (Reel 31, Frame 109)
        - Regis College, 1988-1992 (Reel 31, Frame 182)
        - 'Review of The Library Automation Program: Final Report to the Charles E. Culpeper Foundation' by Ellen Arrick, January 29, 1993 (Reel 31, Frame 238)
        - Review of the Library Automation Program: Planning and Production by Ellen Arrick, 1992-1993 (Reel 31, Frame 293)
        - Review of the Library Automation Program: Project Status Report by Ellen Arrick, 1992-1993 (Reel 31, Frame 435)
        - Roger Williams College, 1990-1992 (Reel 31, Frame 585)
        - Simmons College, 1989, 1991-1992, 1996 (Reel 31, Frame 726)
        - Southeastern Wisconsin Information Technology Exchange (SWITCH), 1991-1993 (Reel 31, Frame 778)
        - University of Connecticut, 1983-1989 (Reel 31, Frame 850)
        - University of Maine, 1990-1992 (Reel 31, Frame 948)
        - Warren Wilson College, 1984, 1992-1995 (Reel 31, Frame 1031)
        - Wellesley College, 1988-1992 (Reel 31, Frame 1086)
        - Widener University, 1989, 1991-1993 (Reel 31, Frame 1127)
      - Library Preservation Grants, 1982-1997; 4
        These grants addressed the preservation and conservation of materials in college and university libraries through development programs, including the enhancement of storage facilities and, in some cases, the construction of conservation laboratories.
        Series 3.4.4 is arranged alphabetically by institution name.
        - Series 3.4.4 - Grants - Education Grants - Library Preservation Grants, 1982-1997 (Reel 31, Frame 1193)
        - College of William and Mary, 1991-1995 (Reel 31, Frame 1194)
        - Colgate University, 1982-1992 (Reel 32, Frame 1)
        - Colgate University - Charles E. Culpeper Laboratory for Conservation of Books and Manuscripts, 1992 (Reel 32, Frame 180)
        - Commission on Preservation and Access, 1992-1997 (Reel 32, Frame 217)
        - The John Carter Brown Library, 1986-1991 (Reel 32, Frame 363)
      - Secondary School Grants, 1974-1996; 5
        The Foundation supported grants to secondary schools, by invitation only due to the limitation of resources, in support of the liberal arts and sciences.
        Series 3.4.5 is arranged in two sub-sub-subseries:
        Sub-sub-subseries 1 - Faculty Renewal Program Grants
        Sub-sub-subseries 2 - Secondary School General Grants
        - Grants - Education Grants - Secondary School Grants - Faculty Renewal Program Grants, 1974-1996; 1
          This grant program offered incentives to inspire the teaching staffs of private secondary schools in the New England and mid-Atlantic states.
          Series 3.4.5.1 is arranged alphabetically by institution name.
          - Series 3.4.5.1 - Grants - Education Grants - Secondary School Grants - Faculty Renewal Program Grants, 1974-1996 (Reel 32, Frame 440)
          - 'Adventurous Teachers, Excellent Schools: A Report to the Culpeper Foundation' by Thomas James, PhD, 1991-1992 (Reel 32, Frame 441)
          - Coalition of Essential Schools, 1979-1983 (Reel 32, Frame 542)
          - Coalition of Essential Schools, 1984-1989 (Reel 32, Frame 767)
          - Coalition of Essential Schools, 1990-1991 (Reel 32, Frame 917)
          - Coalition of Essential Schools, 1992-1996 (Reel 32, Frame 1172)
          - Faculty Renewal Program Applicants (A-L), 1986, 1988-1992 (Reel 33, Frame 1)
          - Faculty Renewal Program Applicants (M-W), 1981-1986, 1988-1992 (Reel 33, Frame 194)
          - Faculty Renewal Program Grants - Correspondence, 1986-1991 (Reel 33, Frame 406)
          - Marketing and Promotional Material, 1990-1992 (Reel 33, Frame 522)
          - Boston College High School, 1985-1991 (Reel 33, Frame 728)
          - Brophy College Preparatory, 1990-1993 (Reel 33, Frame 953)
          - Bryn Mawr School, 1990-1993 (Reel 33, Frame 1069)
          - Buckingham Browne & Nichols School, 1988-1991 (Reel 33, Frame 1130)
          - Cardinal Spellman High School, 1990-1993 (Reel 33, Frame 1179)
          - Catlin Gabel School, 1979, 1985-1993 (Reel 33, Frame 1228)
          - Choate Rosemary Hall, 1988-1991 (Reel 34, Frame 1)
          - Cranbrook Kingswood, 1989-1992 (Reel 34, Frame 84)
          - Fountain Valley School, 1981, 1988-1991 (Reel 34, Frame 148)
          - Germantown Friends School, 1979, 1988-1993 (Reel 34, Frame 304)
          - Gonzaga College High School, 1974, 1978-1992 (Reel 34, Frame 377)
          - Hopkins Grammar Day Prospect Hill School, 1979, 1986-1990 (Reel 34, Frame 458)
          - Isidore Newman School, 1990-1993 (Reel 34, Frame 528)
          - King and Low-Heywood Thomas School, 1981, 1986-1990 (Reel 34, Frame 562)
          - Lakeside School, 1990-1993 (Reel 34, Frame 621)
          - Millbrook School, 1975, 1977-1980, 1982, 1988, 1992 (Reel 34, Frame 680)
          - Miss Porter's School, 1980, 1982, 1986-1990 (Reel 34, Frame 873)
          - Northfield and Mount Hermon School, 1979, 1981, 1984, 1986-1991 (Reel 34, Frame 930)
          - Phillips Academy, 1977-1978, 1981, 1986, 1988-1992 (Reel 34, Frame 1014)
          - Phillips Exeter Academy, 1980-1981, 1989-1999 (Reel 34, Frame 1063)
          - Rice High School, 1982-1991 (Reel 34, Frame 1138)
          - St. Alban's School, 1988-1991 (Reel 35, Frame 1)
          - St. Catherine's School, 1989-1992 (Reel 35, Frame 118)
          - St. Christopher's School, 1990-1992 (Reel 35, Frame 173)
          - St. John's School, 1990-1993 (Reel 35, Frame 226)
          - St. Paul Academy and Summit School, 1979, 1990-1993 (Reel 35, Frame 483)
          - St. Stephen's Episcopal School, 1989-1995 (Reel 35, Frame 543)
          - San Francisco University High School, 1979, 1988-1991 (Reel 35, Frame 630)
          - Sidwell Friends School, 1989-1991 (Reel 35, Frame 675)
          - Taft School, 1986-1988 (Reel 35, Frame 784)
          - Taft School, 1989-1990 (Reel 35, Frame 878)
          - Thacher School, 1989-1991 (Reel 35, Frame 1005)
          - Thomas Jefferson School, 1981, 1988-1991 (Reel 35, Frame 1047)
          - Webb School, 1990-1992 (Reel 35, Frame 1084)
        - Grants - Education Grants - Secondary School Grants - Secondary School General Grants, 1979-1995; 2
          This grant program supported private secondary schools, many in New England and the metropolitan New York area.
          Series 3.4.5.2 is arranged alphabetically by institution name.
          - Series 3.4.5.2 - Grants - Education Grants - Secondary School Grants - Secondary School General Grants, 1979-1995 (Reel 35, Frame 1158)
          - Grant Recommendations, 1979-1989 (Reel 35, Frame 1159)
          - Grant Proposal Reviews, 1988-1993 (Reel 36, Frame 1)
          - General Grants, 1979-1995 (Reel 36, Frame 109)
          - The Athenian School, 1981, 1983 (Reel 36, Frame 110)
          - The Bush School, 1981 (Reel 36, Frame 118)
          - Buxton School, 1981 (Reel 36, Frame 121)
          - Castilleja School, 1980 (Reel 36, Frame 124)
          - The Cathedral School of St. Mary, 1979 (Reel 36, Frame 131)
          - The Catlin Gabel School, 1979 (Reel 36, Frame 135)
          - Central Catholic High School, 1979-1980 (Reel 36, Frame 139)
          - Choate Rosemary Hall, 1979-1980, 1985-1988 (Reel 36, Frame 143)
          - The College Preparatory School, 1980, 1988 (Reel 36, Frame 170)
          - Concord Academy, 1979 (Reel 36, Frame 180)
          - Dana Hall School, 1980 (Reel 36, Frame 185)
          - Darlington School, 1981 (Reel 36, Frame 191)
          - Dublin School, 1979-1980 (Reel 36, Frame 194)
          - The Ethel Walker School, 1980 (Reel 36, Frame 202)
          - Fordham Preparatory School, 1979 (Reel 36, Frame 209)
          - Fountain Valley School, 1981 (Reel 36, Frame 214)
          - Francis W. Parker School, 1979 (Reel 36, Frame 217)
          - Germantown Friends School, 1979 (Reel 36, Frame 222)
          - Gonzaga College High School, 1981 (Reel 36, Frame 229)
          - Groton School, 1980, 1987-1988, 1990 (Reel 36, Frame 232)
          - The Gunnery, 1981-1982 (Reel 36, Frame 242)
          - The Hammonasset School, 1979 (Reel 36, Frame 249)
          - The Hill School, 1981 (Reel 36, Frame 253)
          - The Hotchkiss School, 1980-1981 (Reel 36, Frame 257)
          - La Salle Academy, 1980 (Reel 36, Frame 265)
          - The Loomis-Chaffee School, 1981 (Reel 36, Frame 273)
          - Low-Heywood Thomas School, 1981-1982, 1988 (Reel 36, Frame 276)
          - McQuaid Jesuit High School, 1980-1981 (Reel 36, Frame 282)
          - Millbrook School, 1980 (Reel 36, Frame 294)
          - Miss Porter's School, Farmington, 1980 (Reel 36, Frame 300)
          - The Mountain School, 1979-1980 (Reel 36, Frame 303)
          - Phillips Academy, 1980, 1989 (Reel 36, Frame 306)